To have a wealth transfer to a younger generation who trust their phones and code, AI is part
为了将财富转移给信任手机和代码的年轻一代，人工智能是其中的一部分
of their lives.
他们的生活。
They're not AI immigrants, they're AI natives.
他们不是人工智能移民，而是人工智能原住民。
And when you compound that with this idea of agents, which were unheard of two to three
当你将其与代理人的想法相结合时，这是闻所未闻的两到三个
years ago, our financial lives are going to change.
几年前，我们的财务生活将会发生变化。
Imagine a world in 2027 where you have a traditional bank account which has a crypto or on-chain
想象一下 2027 年的世界，您拥有一个传统的银行账户，其中包含加密货币或链上账户
digital wallet with it.
数字钱包与它。
Imagine you have a crypto wallet that's linked to your bank and to your phone.
想象一下，您有一个与您的银行和手机相连的加密钱包。
Imagine a world where every time you get a paycheck, your agent immediately takes your
想象一下这样一个世界：每当你拿到薪水时，你的经纪人就会立即拿走你的钱。
money, puts it in the highest yielding bank account.
钱，存入收益最高的银行账户。
Or imagine every time you get a bonus or an inheritance or on a Chinese New Year, a red
或者想象一下，每当你获得奖金、遗产或农历新年时，红色
envelope, your agent understands your financial goals and is putting that money into Tesla
信封，你的代理人了解你的财务目标，并将这笔钱投入特斯拉
or a bond or an index fund.
或债券或指数基金。
Imagine you then own these assets in tokenized form.
想象一下，您随后以代币化形式拥有这些资产。
That is how stocks and bonds are going to exist next year.
这就是明年股票和债券的存在方式。
Imagine they can then take that stock or bond and lend it through your wallet to give you
想象一下，他们可以拿走股票或债券，并通过你的钱包借给你
additional yield.
额外的产量。
And then every month or every night, it can look at your goals, it can look at your portfolio
然后每个月或每天晚上，它可以查看您的目标，它可以查看您的投资组合
and automatically rebalance it.
并自动重新平衡它。
So what I'm suggesting is in a world where young people don't have access to institutional
所以我建议的是，在一个年轻人无法接触到机构的世界里
tools that are reserved for Wall Street and the largest banks, in a world where young
在一个年轻人的世界中，这些工具是为华尔街和最大的银行保留的
people feel like they're falling behind financially, an agentic machine economy can help you bridge
人们感觉自己在经济上落后了，代理机器经济可以帮助你弥补这一问题
that gap, can get you better yields, better returns that can help you save for your first
这个差距可以为您带来更好的收益，更好的回报，可以帮助您为您的第一次储蓄
apartment, for a goal, for your child's wedding.
公寓，为了一个目标，为了你孩子的婚礼。
And this is going to happen as your digital twin.
这将作为您的数字孪生发生。
Remember that word.
记住这个词。
Your bank is going to have a Web 3 wallet, you're not even going to know it's the blockchain
您的银行将拥有一个 Web 3 钱包，您甚至不会知道它是区块链
and your digital twin will follow your instructions.
您的数字孪生将遵循您的指示。
The final thing I'll say is I really enjoyed the previous speaker and he said something
我要说的最后一件事是我真的很喜欢之前的演讲者，他说了一些话
interesting that you will be the master of your agent, not your agent.
有趣的是，你将成为你的代理人的主人，而不是你的代理人。
And I agree and I disagree.
我同意，我不同意。
You will be in control of your agent, but you learn from masters.
您将控制您的代理，但您可以向大师学习。
Remember the great scholars in China, you learned at the feet of your masters.
记住中国的伟大学者，你们是在你们老师的脚下学习的。
So while you will have governance over your agent, your agent will teach you how to invest.
因此，虽然您可以管理您的代理人，但您的代理人将教您如何投资。
Your agent will teach you how to rebalance your portfolio.
您的经纪人将教您如何重新平衡您的投资组合。
Your agent will teach you how to achieve your goals.
您的经纪人将教您如何实现您的目标。
So while you control your agent, it could be a master to you to help you achieve better
因此，当您控制您的代理时，它可能会成为您的大师，帮助您取得更好的成就
things in life than you can achieve on your own.
生活中的事情是你自己无法实现的。
And your agent doesn't lie and your agent doesn't sleep and your agent will obey you.
你的经纪人不会说谎，你的经纪人不会睡觉，你的经纪人会服从你。
That is the future we see in front of us sooner than we imagine.
这就是我们比想象中更早看到的未来。
It's very exciting, a lot of new development implementations.
这是非常令人兴奋的，有很多新的开发实现。
And I know you will come back to Hong Kong and I hope I can see you soon.
我知道你会回到香港，我希望很快就能见到你。
But as a final question, when next time you're back to Hong Kong, what change do you expect
但最后一个问题是，下次你回到香港时，你期望发生什么变化
to see in terms of technology, in terms of ecosystem and the world role do you expect
从技术、生态系统和世界角色的角度来看你期望什么
shop playing to play as a core Ethereum ecosystem players?
玩店玩玩以太坊生态系统核心玩家？
I would hope and expect a few things.
我希望并期待一些事情。
One is it's not enough to pass stable coin legislation.
一是仅仅通过稳定币立法还不够。
The stable coins have to grow in circulation and they have to be used to make crypto payments.
稳定币的流通量必须增加，并且必须用于进行加密支付。
They have to be used by corporate treasuries of the largest institutions.
它们必须由最大机构的企业金库使用。
They have to be used in commerce and they have to be used eventually in agentic payments.
它们必须用于商业，并且最终必须用于代理支付。
You're not using a physical piece of paper for these agents to make micro payments.
您没有使用实体纸张让这些代理进行小额支付。
It'll happen with stable coins.
稳定币会发生这种情况。
I hope that the regulators will meet with the industry and think about how some of the
我希望监管机构能够与行业会面，思考一些问题
financial markets can be existing in digital format.
金融市场可以以数字形式存在。
Like in the US where the New York Stock Exchange and the NASDAQ, two of the largest capital
比如在美国，纽约证券交易所和纳斯达克是两个最大的资本市场
markets in the world are going to start trading on a tokenized basis 24-7.
世界各地的市场将开始全天候 24 小时进行代币化交易。
But what I'm most looking forward to is going back to West Kowloon to the Ethereum community
但我最期待的是回到西九龙去以太坊社区
hub and I hope it's filled with young people who are building and innovating and I hope
我希望这里充满了正在建设和创新的年轻人，我希望
to listen and learn to what they're building.
倾听并了解他们正在建造的东西。
That's what I'm looking forward to the next time I come here.
这就是我下次来到这里时所期待的。
SharpLink's role is to give investors opportunity to get access to this once in a lifetime Ethereum
SharpLink 的作用是让投资者有机会接触到这个千载难逢的以太坊
transformation.
转变。
Buy a single stock on NASDAQ.
在纳斯达克购买一只股票。
We hope to raise capital here, but we also help to come invest in the local community
我们希望在这里筹集资金，但我们也帮助投资当地社区
through staking and through partnerships.
通过质押和伙伴关系。
If you own Ether, you have a responsibility to be part of the ecosystem and make it better.
如果您拥有以太币，您就有责任成为生态系统的一部分并使其变得更好。
So I'm humbled to be here.
所以我很荣幸来到这里。
I'm also quite excited to look back in three months or six months and I'll maybe leave
我也很兴奋三个月或六个月后回顾，我可能会离开
you with a quote from one of the greatest American innovators named Bill Gates.
请引用美国最伟大的创新者之一比尔·盖茨的名言。
For those of you who think I'm describing science fiction or something that you won't
对于那些认为我在描述科幻小说或你不会描述的东西的人
see in the next year or two, Bill Gates had a great quote.
看看在接下来的一两年里，比尔·盖茨有一句很棒的话。
He was the leader of Microsoft, one of the most transformative enterprise software companies
他是微软的领导者，微软是最具变革性的企业软件公司之一
in the world, and he basically said that human beings overestimate what can be accomplished
在世界上，他基本上说人类高估了可以完成的事情
by an individual, a team, or technology in one year.
由个人、团队或技术在一年内完成。
We overestimate the impact of one year's innovation, but humans fundamentally underestimate the
我们高估了一年创新的影响，但人类从根本上低估了
impact of an individual contributor, a builder, or a technology is going to have in a decade.
个人贡献者、构建者或技术将在十年内产生影响。
We never would have imagined that AI in the year 2020 would have the impact it has today.
我们从来没有想到2020年的人工智能会产生今天的影响。
We are fundamentally underestimating the level of prosperity and autonomy and access that
我们从根本上低估了繁荣、自治和准入的水平
these technologies will provide, and you won't think of them as crypto.
这些技术将提供，并且您不会将它们视为加密货币。
You'll just think of them as the new user interface for the future of finance and commerce.
您只会将它们视为未来金融和商业的新用户界面。
So don't underestimate what's coming, lean in, learn, and participate, and stay true
因此，不要低估即将发生的事情，积极学习、参与并保持真实
to the principles that we're talking about in the Ethereum community.
我们在以太坊社区中讨论的原则。
Well, Joseph, I cannot learn enough from you, and I would love to carry on the conversation,
好吧，约瑟夫，我从你身上学到的东西还不够，我很乐意继续谈话，
but with limited time, I certainly hope to continue the conversation the next time you're
但由于时间有限，我当然希望下次你来的时候继续谈话
coming back to Hong Kong, and I hope to see you soon in Hong Kong.
我即将回到香港，希望很快能在香港见到你。
Thank you so much for the time today.
非常感谢您今天抽出时间。
Thank you, and thank you to SNZ.
谢谢你，也谢谢SNZ。
Thank you both.
谢谢你们俩。
If you leave the stage, please take a picture.
如果您离开舞台，请拍照留念。
Please give them a round of applause.
请给他们热烈的掌声。
Thank you.
谢谢。
Now, Michael, co-founder and CEO of Brevis on building next-gen dApps with the infinite
现在，Brevis 联合创始人兼首席执行官 Michael 谈论如何构建具有无限能力的下一代 dApp
compute layer.
计算层。
Please welcome Michael.
请欢迎迈克尔。
All right.
好的。
Hello, everyone.
大家好。
This is Michael from Brevis.
这是来自布雷维斯的迈克尔。
Thank you so much for coming to my talk this afternoon, and today I'm going to talk about
非常感谢您今天下午来参加我的演讲，今天我要讲的是
been building at Brevis and how you can build the next generation of decentralized application
Brevis 的构建以及如何构建下一代去中心化应用程序
using infinite computer power that is powered by Brevis.
使用 Brevis 提供的无限计算机能力。
So what is Brevis?
那么布雷维斯是什么？
Brevis is what we call an infinite compute platform, and what it does is it is a ZK-powered
Brevis 是我们所说的无限计算平台，它的作用是它是一个由 ZK 驱动的
verifiable computing platform that enables a lot of new use cases in blockchain applications.
可验证的计算平台，可在区块链应用程序中实现许多新用例。
So before I dive into what we do exactly, let me kind of talk about the challenge we're
因此，在深入探讨我们具体做什么之前，让我先谈谈我们面临的挑战
trying to solve here.
试图在这里解决。
So blockchains themselves are often marketed as word computers.
因此，区块链本身通常被称为文字计算机。
But if you look at all the blockchains that are available today, they simply cannot run
但如果你看看当今所有可用的区块链，它们根本无法运行
faster than a single server, and it is extremely expensive to process transactions on blockchain.
比单个服务器更快，并且在区块链上处理交易极其昂贵。
Well, you may say, OK, wait, wait, wait.
好吧，你可能会说，好吧，等等，等等，等等。
This cannot be the case because we have been building blockchain scalability technology
事实并非如此，因为我们一直在构建区块链可扩展性技术
for years, so we should be able to build anything on blockchain today, right?
多年来，所以我们今天应该能够在区块链上构建任何东西，对吗？
Well, unfortunately, that is not the case.
不幸的是，事实并非如此。
Let me give you a very concrete example here.
让我在这里给你一个非常具体的例子。
So if you have ever used any centralized exchanges in the past, you all have used this kind of
所以如果你过去用过中心化交易所的话，你都用过这种
feature where if you trade it loud in this month, in the next month, you get a trading
如果您在本月大声交易，则在下个月，您将获得交易
fee discount, right?
费用折扣，对吗？
So this is a bread and butter user retaining feature for centralized exchanges.
因此，这是中心化交易所的一项重要的用户保留功能。
You would imagine this kind of a feature will be available on every decentralized exchanges
你会想象这种功能将在每个去中心化交易所上提供
like Uniswap, PancakeSwap, and everywhere, right?
比如 Uniswap、PancakeSwap 等等，对吧？
But it's not actually the case.
但实际情况并非如此。
None of them have this feature.
他们都没有这个功能。
And it's not because they don't want to build this.
这并不是因为他们不想建造这个。
It's actually because they're building this feature on blockchain directly requires a
这实际上是因为他们在区块链上构建这个功能直接需要一个
level of computation that is not available in today's blockchain because it's too expensive.
当今的区块链无法提供这样的计算级别，因为它太昂贵了。
Well, why is that?
嗯，这是为什么呢？
We want to ask why blockchains are actually this expensive, right?
我们想问为什么区块链实际上这么贵，对吧？
Well, it is actually deeply rooted in how blockchains work today.
嗯，它实际上深深植根于当今区块链的运作方式。
So blockchain is operated by something called distributed consensus, and you have a lot
所以区块链是通过分布式共识来运作的，而且你有很多
of different nodes in the blockchain network, and everyone is computing the same thing,
区块链网络中的不同节点，每个人都在计算相同的东西，
so they can reach agreement on certain computation result and kind of move the blockchain forward.
这样他们就可以就某些计算结果达成一致，并推动区块链向前发展。
So let's say we have this two-node blockchain where we have Alice and Bob here, and Alice
假设我们有一个双节点区块链，其中有 Alice 和 Bob，Alice
is trying to compute the result of this multiplication equation, and then Alice is now trying to
正在尝试计算这个乘法方程的结果，然后爱丽丝现在正在尝试
convince Bob this is actually the correct result.
说服鲍勃这实际上是正确的结果。
So what does Bob do here?
那么鲍勃在这里做什么呢？
Well, the only way for Bob to actually reach consensus with Alice is to do the computation again.
那么，Bob 真正与 Alice 达成共识的唯一方法就是再次进行计算。
So this is okay, but this is actually problematic because a very simple kind of a computation
所以这没关系，但这实际上是有问题的，因为一种非常简单的计算
that is, let's say you want to swap token A to token B on blockchain is now actually
也就是说，假设您现在想在区块链上将代币 A 交换为代币 B
replicated a million times on blockchains like Ethereum because you have actually a
在像以太坊这样的区块链上复制一百万次，因为你实际上有一个
million different kind of nodes in Ethereum, and that is why replicated computing is making
以太坊中有数百万个不同类型的节点，这就是复制计算正在创造的原因
blockchain extremely expensive to use.
区块链的使用极其昂贵。
Well, so how do we solve this?
那么我们该如何解决这个问题呢？
Well, we can solve this by using a new concept called verifiable computing.
好吧，我们可以通过使用一种称为可验证计算的新概念来解决这个问题。
In verifiable computing, you have different roles in the computing process.
在可验证计算中，您在计算过程中扮演不同的角色。
So you have Alice as not only the computing provider, but also a proof generator.
因此，Alice 不仅是计算提供者，而且还是证明生成器。
So Alice is not only just doing the computing, but also generates a mathematical piece, a
所以爱丽丝不仅在做计算，而且还生成了一个数学片段，一个
magical piece of mathematical proof called zero-knowledge proof.
神奇的数学证明称为零知识证明。
So the zero-knowledge proof is a very magical thing here that Alice can send to Bob here
所以零知识证明在这里是一个非常神奇的东西，Alice可以在这里发送给Bob
so that Bob can verify the computation is done correctly without actually rerunning
这样鲍勃就可以验证计算是否正确完成，而无需实际重新运行
the computation again.
再次计算。
And this is very important because no matter how complex the original computation is, the
这一点非常重要，因为无论原始计算多么复杂，
verification cost is always tiny and the verification latency is always very low.
验证成本总是很小，验证延迟总是很低。
And with this new primitive, we can build new kind of blockchains and even new kind
有了这个新的原语，我们可以构建新类型的区块链，甚至新类型
of blockchain applications because now, you know, we don't actually need to run everything
区块链应用程序，因为现在我们实际上不需要运行所有内容
on blockchain themselves.
关于区块链本身。
We can actually offload very complex and heavy computation away from blockchain to this off-chain
我们实际上可以将非常复杂和繁重的计算从区块链转移到链下
environment that we built called Brevis.
我们构建的环境称为 Brevis。
And inside of Brevis, you can actually do the computation but also generate a zero-knowledge
在 Brevis 内部，您实际上可以进行计算，但也可以生成零知识
proof and you can bring the zero-knowledge proof back to the blockchain and the blockchain
证明，你可以把零知识证明带回区块链和区块链
can use the computation result as if the entire computation happened on blockchain directly.
可以使用计算结果，就好像整个计算直接发生在区块链上一样。
The most important thing here is that this entire process does not actually introduce
这里最重要的是，这整个过程实际上并没有引入
any additional trust assumptions and is as secure as if you're just doing everything
任何额外的信任假设，并且就像您正在做所有事情一样安全
on blockchain directly but at the same time, extremely low cost because the blockchains
直接在区块链上，但同时成本极低，因为区块链
themselves are just verifying the computation result instead of actually doing the computation.
他们只是验证计算结果而不是实际进行计算。
So Brevis is actually massively used in production today and we have great adoption across, for
因此，Brevis 实际上在今天的生产中得到了广泛的应用，并且我们在各个方面都得到了广泛的采用，例如
example, the DeFi ecosystem and some of the biggest attacks today like PancakeSwap, Uniswap,
例如，DeFi 生态系统和当今一些最大的攻击，如 PancakeSwap、Uniswap、
are using us to build their user customisation and intelligent DeFi features.
正在使用我们来构建他们的用户定制和智能 DeFi 功能。
And we're also powering growth on things like Linea, BNB chain and many others.
我们还推动 Linea、BNB 链和许多其他项目的增长。
For example, we have helped Linea to launch their entire blockchain through a program
例如，我们帮助 Linea 通过一个程序启动了他们的整个区块链
called Linea Ignition Program that allows you to actually distribute the network token
称为 Linea Ignition 程序，允许您实际分发网络令牌
to users with ZK proof.
给有ZK证明的用户。
And we have also been helping and building alongside of our reward asset partners especially
我们也一直在帮助和建设我们的奖励资产合作伙伴，特别是
in the stable token space that we help them to grow the stable token and so many others.
在稳定代币领域，我们帮助他们发展稳定代币和许多其他代币。
So I mentioned like we have a lot of adoptions but what is actually Brevis?
所以我提到我们有很多采用，但 Brevis 到底是什么？
What is actually inside this magic box?
这个神奇的盒子里到底装着什么？
Well, the centerpiece of our entire computing stack is something called a Pico ZKVM.
嗯，我们整个计算堆栈的核心是 Pico ZKVM。
So what is a ZKVM?
那么什么是 ZKVM？
Well, ZKVM is a general purpose virtual machine that you can run any program on top of it.
那么，ZKVM 是一个通用虚拟机，您可以在其上运行任何程序。
And it's ZK and the ZK enabled means that you can actually run any program and generate
它是 ZK，启用 ZK 意味着您实际上可以运行任何程序并生成
a verifiable proof of the program's computing result.
程序计算结果的可验证证明。
Now ZK or like kind of a cryptographic proof is actually very hard to learn mathematical
现在 ZK 或类似的密码学证明实际上很难学习数学
concept.
概念。
Before you have something like Pico ZKVM, all you can do is actually write the program
在你拥有像 Pico ZKVM 这样的东西之前，你所能做的就是实际编写程序
in mathematical equations if you want to kind of make it a provable.
如果你想证明它是在数学方程中。
But with ZKVM, what you can do is you can just write very high level language just like
但是使用 ZKVM，你可以做的是你可以编写非常高级的语言，就像
you write any software and then you can make this entire program provable and verifiable.
你编写任何软件，然后你就可以使整个程序可证明和可验证。
So this is also how we're changing how blockchains are built and operated today.
因此，这也是我们改变当今区块链构建和运营方式的方式。
So Ethereum itself is actually moving towards a ZK oriented architecture.
所以以太坊本身实际上正在走向面向ZK的架构。
So instead of every validator in Ethereum, like millions of them, repeat the same kind
因此，不要像以太坊中的每个验证器那样，像数以百万计的那样，重复相同的类型
of computation again and again.
一次又一次的计算。
What now you can do is to have one validator do a very large amount of computation and
现在您可以做的是让一个验证器执行大量计算，并且
generate a very small proof that you can use so that everyone else can just verify the
生成一个您可以使用的非常小的证明，以便其他人可以验证
proof of the computation is done correctly and then the blockchain can move forward.
证明计算正确完成，然后区块链就可以继续前进。
What this means is that you can actually use any hardware you have today, like even on
这意味着您实际上可以使用现在拥有的任何硬件，甚至在
your phone, to run a full node of Ethereum and reach maximal decentralization and at
您的手机，运行以太坊的完整节点并达到最大程度的去中心化
the same time maximal scalability.
同时具有最大的可扩展性。
Like I'm talking about a hundred times better scalability of today's Ethereum blockchain.
就像我正在谈论当今以太坊区块链的可扩展性提高一百倍一样。
So to do this, what you need is an extremely fast ZK VM so that you can actually catch
因此，要做到这一点，您需要一个非常快的 ZK VM，以便您可以真正捕获
up with the blockchain production time.
与区块链生产时间同步。
Like for Ethereum blocks it is produced every 12 seconds, so you need to actually be able
与以太坊区块一样，它每 12 秒生成一次，因此您实际上需要能够
to generate the proof of block execution within that 12 seconds.
生成 12 秒内区块执行的证明。
And this is what we do, ZK VM is as fast as ZK VM that allows you to generate the ZK proof
这就是我们所做的，ZK VM 与 ZK VM 一样快，可以让您生成 ZK 证明
for a blockchain execution within 12 seconds for 99% of Ethereum blocks.
区块链在 12 秒内执行 99% 的以太坊区块。
So as I mentioned there are numerous kind of use cases that you can use Brevis to build
正如我提到的，您可以使用 Brevis 构建多种用例
but I want to first share today with you that some of the use cases are even beyond just
但今天我想首先与大家分享的是，有些用例甚至超出了
the blockchain applications.
区块链应用。
We're actually actively working on some AI-based applications.
我们实际上正在积极开发一些基于人工智能的应用程序。
So I'm very happy to introduce a new product we built called Brevis Vera.
所以我很高兴向大家介绍我们开发的一款新产品 Brevis Vera。
We're trying to solve a very critical problem in Brevis Vera today, that is if you see a
今天我们正试图解决 Brevis Vera 的一个非常关键的问题，那就是如果你看到
viral media, like a viral photo or viral movie or video online, the first question now you
病毒式媒体，例如病毒式照片或病毒式电影或在线视频，现在的第一个问题是
ask is always, is this actually real, is a video actually generated by AI or not?
总是有人问，这真的是真的吗？视频真的是由人工智能生成的吗？
Well, one way you can do this is to use AI to defeat AI, use an AI model to defeat or
好吧，你可以做到这一点的一种方法是使用人工智能来击败人工智能，使用人工智能模型来击败或
to detect whether a video or a photo is actually generated by AI, but that is a never-ending
检测视频或照片是否真的是由人工智能生成的，但这是一个永无止境的过程
arms race because you never can beat an AI with another AI.
军备竞赛，因为你永远无法用另一个人工智能击败一个人工智能。
So what we're here trying to do is to provide a different solution that enables you to generate
所以我们在这里试图做的是提供一个不同的解决方案，使您能够生成
a test station of what is real.
真实的测试站。
So we're not detecting what is fake, we're actually testing what is real.
所以我们不是在检测什么是假的，我们实际上是在测试什么是真的。
So we enable you to essentially start your entire test station chain from your device
因此，我们使您能够从您的设备上启动整个测试站链
capture.
捕获。
So when you're capturing a photo on your device, you get a cryptographic signature of the raw
因此，当您在设备上拍摄照片时，您会获得原始照片的加密签名
data.
数据。
And then even if you added all this data, even if you added all this kind of video,
然后即使你添加了所有这些数据，即使你添加了所有这种视频，
we can use our ZKVM to generate a zero-knowledge proof to show that the end result of the
我们可以使用 ZKVM 生成零知识证明来表明最终结果
video or photo that you show is actually coming from a real device capture instead of generated
您显示的视频或照片实际上来自真实设备捕获而不是生成
by AI.
通过人工智能。
So this way, you can solve the AI deep fake problem 100%.
所以这样一来，就可以100%解决AI深度造假问题。
There's no kind of a fake, you know, AI deep fake possibility as long as you can prove
只要你能证明，就不存在任何造假的可能性，你知道，人工智能深度造假的可能性
the video you upload or the image you upload is actually real.
您上传的视频或您上传的图片实际上是真实的。
So you know, Brevis Vera's beta is already live and we're working and talking to some
所以你知道，Brevis Vera 的测试版已经上线，我们正在与一些人合作和交谈
of the biggest photo editing companies in the world and digital media editing companies
世界上最大的照片编辑公司和数字媒体编辑公司
in the world to integrate Vera in their core product.
世界上将 Vera 集成到他们的核心产品中。
And you know, another very important category of application we power is something called
你知道，我们支持的另一个非常重要的应用程序类别是
Intelligent DeFi.
智能 DeFi。
So for example, we're working with PancakeSwap and to power their kind of a, you know, plug-in
例如，我们正在与 PancakeSwap 合作，为他们的插件提供支持
based, you know, DAX's approach that allows you to essentially customize user experience
您知道，基于 DAX 的方法可以让您从本质上定制用户体验
based on user's historical interaction with the protocol and application.
基于用户与协议和应用程序的历史交互。
So for example, now in PancakeSwap, if you actually swapped a lot in this month, and
举例来说，现在在 PancakeSwap 中，如果您这个月实际上交换了很多，并且
you can use Brevis to generate a ZK proof and get a trading fee discount in the next
您可以使用Brevis生成ZK证明并在接下来获得交易费折扣
month.
月。
So you know, another side of Brevis and another side of ZK, you know, in a...
所以你知道，Brevis 的另一面和 ZK 的另一面，你知道，在......